(this["webpackJsonpreact-quiz"]=this["webpackJsonpreact-quiz"]||[]).push([[0],{121:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n.p+"static/media/logo.ee9e8b1b.svg"},124:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(282)},129:function(e,t,n){},279:function(e,t,n){},282:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var o=n(0),r=n.n(o),i=n(76),a=n.n(i),c=n(51),s=(n(129),n(26)),l=n(27),u=n(28),p=n(32),m=n(29),d=n(46),y=n(33),h=n(8),f=[{question:"In which decade did AI formal research begin?",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"1950s"},{type:"incorrect",content:"1930s"},{type:"incorrect",content:"1980s"},{type:"incorrect",content:"2000s "}]},{question:"The area of AI which investigates methods of facilitating the textual interactions between people and computers is:",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Machine learning"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Symbolic processing"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Decision Support"},{type:"correct",content:"Natural language processing"}]},{question:"The practice of using algorithms to parse data, learn from it, and then make a determination or prediction about something is:",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"Machine learning"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Symbolic processing"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Decision Support"},{type:"incorrect",content:"None of These"}]},{question:"Which of the following methods is NOT a learning method?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Memorization"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Analogy"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Deduction"},{type:"correct",content:"Introduction"}]},{question:"Which programming language is commonly used for AI?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"C++/C"},{type:"correct",content:"Python"},{type:"incorrect",content:"PHP"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Java"}]},{question:"Who is considered as the father of artificial intelligence?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Donald Trump"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Kim Jong-Un"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Vladimir Putin"},{type:"correct",content:"Alan Turing"}]},{question:"How does a decision tree make a decision?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"After a single test"},{type:"incorrect",content:"After two tests"},{type:"correct",content:"After a sequence of tests"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Without a test"}]},{question:"Which of the following takes an object described by a set of attributes as an input?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Random forest"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Decision graph"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Decision tree"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"What are the tasks an AI system can perform?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Act as a virtual assistant"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Automate manual processes"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Analyze unstructured data"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"A software designed to simulate a conversation between a computer and a human end user is called:",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"ChatBot"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Scream"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Sharepoint"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Walkie Talkie"}]},{question:"While evaluating the performance of a classifier, what do we mean by the sensitivity of our model?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"False positive rate"},{type:"correct",content:"True positive rate"},{type:"incorrect",content:"False negative rate"},{type:"incorrect",content:"True negative rate"}]},{question:"Which of the following is true about model capacity (the ability of a neural network to approximate complex functions)?",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"As the number of hidden layers increase, model capacity increases"},{type:"incorrect",content:"As dropout ratio increases, model capacity increases"},{type:"incorrect",content:"As the learning rate increases, model capacity increases"},{type:"incorrect",content:"None of these"}]},{question:"What is(are) an(some) advantage(s) of decision trees?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Possible Scenarios can be added"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Interpretability of the model"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Worst, best and expected values can be determined for different scenarios"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"In unsupervised learning:",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Specific output values are given"},{type:"correct",content:"Output values are not given"},{type:"incorrect",content:"No specific inputs are given"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Both inputs and outputs are given"}]},{question:"Neural Networks are mainly used for modeling complex ______________with many parameters",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Linear Functions "},{type:"correct",content:"Nonlinear Functions"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Discrete Functions"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Exponential Functions"}]},{question:"What is a perceptron?",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"a single layer feed-forward neural network with pre-processing"},{type:"incorrect",content:"an auto-associative neural network"},{type:"incorrect",content:"a double layer auto-associative neural network "},{type:"incorrect",content:"a neural network that contains feedback"}]},{question:"In which of the following learning paradigms the model receives rewards and punishements based on the outcome?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Active Learning"},{type:"correct",content:"Reinforcement Learning "},{type:"incorrect",content:"Supervised learning "},{type:"incorrect",content:"Unsupervised learning"}]},{question:"Decision trees are appropriate for the problems where: ",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"The output is numerical"},{type:"incorrect",content:"The output is nominal categorical"},{type:"incorrect",content:"The output is ordinal categorical"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned "}]},{question:"How can back propagation be defined? ",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Another name given to the polynomial function "},{type:"incorrect",content:"The transmission of error back through the network to adjust the inputs "},{type:"correct",content:"The transmission of error back through the network to adjust weights "},{type:"incorrect",content:"None of these"}]},{question:"What text mining technique can be used for noise reduction?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Lemmatization"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Word embeddings"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Stemming"},{type:"correct",content:"Lemmatization and stemming"}]},{question:"What technique(s) could be used to adjust the parameters and minimize the cost function?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Exhaustive Search"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Random Search"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Bayesian Optimization"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"What could be the reason for the loss not decrease in the first few epochs while training a neural network?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"The learning rate is low"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Regularization parameter is high"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Stuck at local minima"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"Computational learning theory analyzes the sample complexity and computational complexity of:",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Unsupervised Learning"},{type:"correct",content:"Inductive learning"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Forced based learning"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Weak learning"}]},{question:"If the output of a process rejects a hypothesis, but in reality the hypothesis holds, it is a: ",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Type II error"},{type:"incorrect",content:"False negative"},{type:"correct",content:"Type I error"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Specialized hypothesis"}]},{question:"Which of the following is also called exploratory learning?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Supervised learning"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Active learning "},{type:"correct",content:"Unsupervised learning"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Reinforcement learning "}]},{question:"In language processing, which levels of knowledge are not included?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Semantical"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Syntactical"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Pragmatical"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"How is the process of deleting certain neurons at random during the training of a neural network called?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Random subsampling"},{type:"correct",content:"Dropout"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Batch normalization"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Neural killing"}]},{question:"What other name(s) can be given to some decision tree nodes?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Decision Nodes"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Leaves"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Chance Nodes"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"Which of these does NOT use machine learning/AI?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Driverless cars"},{type:"incorrect",content:"SIRI"},{type:"correct",content:"Sonos wireless speakers"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Facial recognition on phone"}]},{question:"Does AI have conscience?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"True"},{type:"correct",content:"False "},{type:"incorrect",content:"Maybe"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Depend of cases"}]},{question:"Which one of these is not an area of AI?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Computer Vison"},{type:"correct",content:"Web design"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Robotics"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Voice recognition"}]},{question:"Which of the following is an application of natural language processing?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Voice assistants like Amazon Alexa and Siri"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Chatbots"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Sentiment analysis"},{type:"correct",content:"All of the above"}]},{question:"Which of the following is NOT an application of computer vision?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Medical imaging"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Autonomous vehicles"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Face recognition"},{type:"correct",content:"Sentiment analysis"}]},{question:"Which of the following is an example of feature extraction?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Removing stop words in a sentence"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Constructing a bag of word vectors from an email"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Applying PCA projects to large, high-dimensional data"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"Which of the following is a necessary characteristic of test datasets?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Representative of the training data as a whole"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Large enough to yield meaningful results"},{type:"incorrect",content:"None of mentioned"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"Why is Weight Initialization important in Neural Networks?",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"To prevent gradient from vanishing during the course of a backward pass"},{type:"incorrect",content:"To increase the accuracy of the model"},{type:"incorrect",content:"To use memory more efficiently"},{type:"incorrect",content:"For regularization purposes"}]}];f.forEach((function(e,t){return e.answers.forEach((function(e,n){"incorrect"===e.type&&(e.type="incorrect-".concat(t,"-").concat(n))}))}));var g=f,w=n(30);var v=function(e){return r.a.createElement("h2",{className:"question"},e.content)};var b=function(e){return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"questionCount"},"Question ",r.a.createElement("span",null,e.counter)," of ",r.a.createElement("span",null,e.total))};var E=function(e){return r.a.createElement("li",{className:"answerOption"},r.a.createElement("input",{type:"radio",className:"radioCustomButton",name:"radioGroup",checked:e.answerType===e.answer,id:e.answerType,value:e.answerType,disabled:e.answer,onChange:e.onAnswerSelected}),r.a.createElement("label",{className:"radioCustomLabel",htmlFor:e.answerType},e.answerContent))};var q=function(e){return r.a.createElement(w.CSSTransitionGroup,{className:"container",component:"div",transitionName:"fade",transitionEnterTimeout:800,transitionLeaveTimeout:500,transitionAppear:!0,transitionAppearTimeout:500},r.a.createElement("div",{key:e.questionId},r.a.createElement(b,{counter:e.questionId,total:e.questionTotal}),r.a.createElement(v,{content:e.question}),r.a.createElement("ul",{className:"answerOptions"},e.answerOptions.map((function(t,n){return r.a.createElement(E,{key:t.content,index:n,answerContent:t.content,answerType:t.type,answer:e.answer,questionId:e.questionId,onAnswerSelected:e.onAnswerSelected})})))))},k=n(1),S=n.n(k),A=n(113),z=function(e){return e.charAt(0).toUpperCase()+e.slice(1)},T=function(e){var t=e.formErrors;return r.a.createElement("div",{style:{display:"flex",justifyContent:"center",alignItems:"center",fontSize:"1.5em"}},Object.keys(t).map((function(e,n){return t[e].length>0?r.a.createElement("p",{style:{color:"rgb(207, 222, 0)"},key:n},z(e)," ",t[e]):""})))},O=n(284),x=n(285),C=n(286),j=n(287),I=function(e){function t(e){var n;return Object(l.a)(this,t),(n=Object(p.a)(this,Object(m.a)(t).call(this,e))).handleUserInput=function(e){var t=e.target.name,o=e.target.value;n.setState(Object(s.a)({},t,o),(function(){n.validateField(t,o)}))},n.state={email:"",formErrors:{email:""},emailValid:!1,formValid:!1},n}return Object(y.a)(t,e),Object(u.a)(t,[{key:"validateField",value:function(e,t){var n=this.state.formErrors,o=this.state.emailValid;switch(e){case"email":o=t.match(/^([\w.%+-]+)@([\w-]+\.)+([\w]{2,})$/i),n.email=o?"":" is invalid"}this.setState({formErrors:n,emailValid:o},this.validateForm)}},{key:"validateForm",value:function(){this.setState({formValid:this.state.emailValid})}},{key:"errorClass",value:function(e){return 0===e.length?"":"has-error"}},{key:"formPreventDefault",value:function(e){e.preventDefault()}},{key:"storeWinnerEmail",value:function(){var e=this.state.email,t=JSON.parse(localStorage.getItem("emails"))||[];t.push(e),localStorage.setItem("emails",JSON.stringify(t)),document.location.reload()}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=Object.keys(this.props.answersCount),t={labels:["Correct","Incorrect"],datasets:[{data:[this.props.answersCount.correct,e.filter((function(e){return"correct"!==e})).length],backgroundColor:["#cfde00","#0071ce"]}]};return r.a.createElement("form",{style:{display:"flex",justifyContent:"center",alignItems:"center",flexDirection:"column",color:"white"},onSubmit:this.formPreventDefault},r.a.createElement("h1",null,"Congratulations, you have won the quizz"),r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement(A.a,{data:t,options:{legend:{display:!0,position:"left",labels:{fontColor:"white",fontFamily:"'PT Sans', sans-serif",fontSize:24}},responsive:!0,maintainAspectRatio:!0}})),r.a.createElement("h1",null,"Participate to the draw and win an iPad !"),r.a.createElement("div",{style:{width:"100%",minHeight:"168px"}},r.a.createElement("div",{style:{display:"flex",justifyContent:"center",alignItems:"center",width:"100%",fontSize:"1.5em"},className:"form-group ".concat(this.errorClass(this.state.formErrors.email))},r.a.createElement("input",{type:"Type your email here...",required:!0,className:"form-control",name:"email",placeholder:"Email",value:this.state.email,onChange:this.handleUserInput,style:{padding:"12px 20px",margin:"14px",boxSizing:"border-box",fontSize:"1em",fontFamily:"PT Sans, sans-serif",borderRadius:"4px"}}),r.a.createElement("button",{style:{background:"#CFDE00",border:"none",color:"#0071ce",padding:"15px 32px",textAlign:"center",textDecoration:"none",display:"inline-block",fontSize:"1em",fontFamily:"PT Sans, sans-serif",borderRadius:"4px",height:"60px"},className:"btn btn-primary",disabled:!this.state.formValid,onClick:this.storeWinnerEmail.bind(this)},"Submit")),r.a.createElement(T,{formErrors:this.state.formErrors})),r.a.createElement("h1",null,"Share your score on social media"),r.a.createElement("div",{style:{display:"flex",width:"20%",justifyContent:"space-between"}},r.a.createElement(O.a,{url:"https://twitter.com/Qiminfo",hashtags:["AMLD2020","QimQuizz","Qiminfo"]},r.a.createElement(x.a,{size:64,round:!0})),r.a.createElement(C.a,{url:"https://www.linkedin.com/company/qim-info"},r.a.createElement(j.a,{size:64,round:!0}))))}}]),t}(o.Component),N=function(){return window.location.reload()};function W(e){var t;return"lost"===e.quizResult&&(t=r.a.createElement("div",{style:{display:"flex",justifyContent:"center",flexDirection:"column",background:"rgb(0, 113, 206)",padding:"24px",color:"white",alignItems:"center"}},r.a.createElement("h2",null,"You failed the quizz..."),r.a.createElement("button",{style:{background:"#cfde00",border:"none",color:"#0071ce",padding:"15px 32px",textAlign:"center",textDecoration:"none",display:"inline-block",fontSize:"1.5em",fontFamily:"PT Sans, sans-serif",borderRadius:"4px"},onClick:N}," Try again"))),"win"===e.quizResult&&(t=r.a.createElement(I,e)),r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,t)}W.propTypes={quizResult:S.a.string.isRequired};var D=W,F=n(121),R=n.n(F);n(279);function P(e,t){var n=Object.keys(e);if(Object.getOwnPropertySymbols){var o=Object.getOwnPropertySymbols(e);t&&(o=o.filter((function(t){return Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptor(e,t).enumerable}))),n.push.apply(n,o)}return n}function Q(e){for(var t=1;t<arguments.length;t++){var n=null!=arguments[t]?arguments[t]:{};t%2?P(n,!0).forEach((function(t){Object(s.a)(e,t,n[t])})):Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptors?Object.defineProperties(e,Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptors(n)):P(n).forEach((function(t){Object.defineProperty(e,t,Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptor(n,t))}))}return e}var L=function(e){function t(e){var n;return Object(l.a)(this,t),(n=Object(p.a)(this,Object(m.a)(t).call(this,e))).state={counter:0,questionId:1,question:"",answerOptions:[],answer:"",answersCount:{},result:"",questionsCount:10,quizzTitle:"Qim Quizz",displayQuizz:!1},n.handleAnswerSelected=n.handleAnswerSelected.bind(Object(d.a)(n)),n}return Object(y.a)(t,e),Object(u.a)(t,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){var e=this,t=this.shuffleArray(g),n=t.map((function(t){return e.shuffleArray(t.answers)}));this.setState({question:t[0].question,answerOptions:n[0]})}},{key:"shuffleArray",value:function(e){for(var t,n,o=e.length;0!==o;)n=Math.floor(Math.random()*o),t=e[o-=1],e[o]=e[n],e[n]=t;return e}},{key:"handleAnswerSelected",value:function(e){var t=this;this.setUserAnswer(e.currentTarget.value),this.state.questionId<this.state.questionsCount?setTimeout((function(){return t.setNextQuestion()}),300):setTimeout((function(){return t.setResults(t.getResults())}),300)}},{key:"setUserAnswer",value:function(e){this.setState((function(t,n){return{answersCount:Q({},t.answersCount,Object(s.a)({},e,(t.answersCount[e]||0)+1)),answer:e}}))}},{key:"setNextQuestion",value:function(){var e=this.state.counter+1,t=this.state.questionId+1;this.setState({counter:e,questionId:t,question:g[e].question,answerOptions:g[e].answers,answer:""})}},{key:"getResults",value:function(){return this.state.answersCount.correct>=this.state.questionsCount/2?"win":"lost"}},{key:"setResults",value:function(e){"lost"===e&&this.setState({displayQuizz:!1}),this.setState({result:e})}},{key:"renderQuiz",value:function(){var e=this.state.displayQuizz;return r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,!e&&r.a.createElement("div",{style:{display:"flex",justifyContent:"center"}},r.a.createElement("button",{style:{background:"#cfde00",border:"none",color:"#0071ce",padding:"15px 32px",textAlign:"center",textDecoration:"none",display:"inline-block",fontSize:"1.5em",fontFamily:"PT Sans, sans-serif",borderRadius:"4px"},onClick:this.displayQuizz.bind(this)}," Get started")),e&&r.a.createElement(q,{answer:this.state.answer,answerOptions:this.state.answerOptions,questionId:this.state.questionId,question:this.state.question,questionTotal:this.state.questionsCount,onAnswerSelected:this.handleAnswerSelected}))}},{key:"displayQuizz",value:function(){this.setState({displayQuizz:!0})}},{key:"renderResult",value:function(){return r.a.createElement(D,Object.assign({},this.state,{quizResult:this.state.result}))}},{key:"render",value:function(){return r.a.createElement(c.a,null,r.a.createElement(w.CSSTransitionGroup,{className:"container result",component:"div",transitionName:"fade",transitionEnterTimeout:800,transitionLeaveTimeout:500,transitionAppear:!0,transitionEnter:!0,transitionLeave:!1,transitionAppearTimeout:500},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"App-header"},r.a.createElement("img",{src:R.a,className:"App-logo",alt:"logo"}),r.a.createElement("h1",{style:{color:"#CFDE00"}}," ",this.state.quizzTitle)),this.state.result?this.renderResult():this.renderQuiz())),r.a.createElement(h.c,null,r.a.createElement(h.a,{path:"/winners",component:V})))}}]),t}(o.Component);function _(e,t){return r.a.createElement("p",{key:t},e)}var V=function(e){function t(){return Object(l.a)(this,t),Object(p.a)(this,Object(m.a)(t).apply(this,arguments))}return Object(y.a)(t,e),Object(u.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e,t=JSON.parse(localStorage.getItem("emails"));return t||(e=r.a.createElement("p",null,"No winners to display")),t&&(e=t.map(_)),r.a.createElement(w.CSSTransitionGroup,{className:"container result",component:"div",transitionName:"fade",transitionEnterTimeout:800,transitionLeaveTimeout:500,transitionAppear:!0,transitionEnter:!0,transitionLeave:!1,transitionAppearTimeout:500},r.a.createElement("h2",null,"Winners"),e)}}]),t}(o.Component),M=L;Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));a.a.render(r.a.createElement(c.a,null,r.a.createElement(M,null)),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(e){e.unregister()}))}},[[124,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.c5b960b2.chunk.js.map